[{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020d5"},"answer":"the positively sloped lines indicate when shifts start. Find 12 pm and follow the positive sloped line up to the event point(s).","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":66538,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69","time_elapsed":741140,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020ee"},"answer":"To determine which events start at 12 pm, go to the x axis, and follow the lines that lean toward the right. If an event (or shift) is on that same line, then it must start at 12 pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121\n121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":114012,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0","time_elapsed":885253,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02107"},"answer":"take 12 pm spot on x-axis as the left bottom mark as a triangle which has the shift name as the top mark.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":75896,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME","time_elapsed":2055459,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02120"},"answer":"there are two lines starting at certain times, the one shooting to the right will meet some lines shooting to the left, when there is an event at their intersection, that event starts at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":266019,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO","time_elapsed":677849,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02139"},"answer":"Look at 12pm on the time axis, and look at the line pointing diagonally to the right from 12. You will find M and L along this line, therefore they begin at 12. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":46054,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1","time_elapsed":393624,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0219d"},"answer":"find 12 on x axis follow diagonal line to the right","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":24765,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP","time_elapsed":498170,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021b6"},"answer":"I begin with looking at the Horizontal axis (Start & end time) and go up from there ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":51771,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ","time_elapsed":2841539,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021cf"},"answer":"go to 12 pm on the x axis and then move up the line towards the right till you see dots of the events","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":27514,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY","time_elapsed":472809,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021e8"},"answer":"be","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":12946,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV","time_elapsed":3607558,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02201"},"answer":"Start on x axis, move right until 12pm, then go up on the line segment that starts at 12pm and goes up to the right (towards M), continue until end of line. M & L both start at 12pm because they both lay on the line up and right starting at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":66393,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX","time_elapsed":400576,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0221a"},"answer":"I find 12pm on the X axis, then I take the diagonal on the right and follow it until I find dots M and L.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":83496,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035","time_elapsed":19949428,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02233"},"answer":"On the X axis of the graph, the start of a shift is marked by the left side of a triangle formed by the 2 lines that emerge below each shift's dot on the graph","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":81749,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41","time_elapsed":1245146,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0224c"},"answer":"1. FIND 12 PM; 2. FOLLOW THE RIGHT, DIAGONAL LINE UP; 3. THESE SHIFTS START AT 12: M, L ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221\n221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":45018,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE","time_elapsed":439075,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02265"},"answer":"1) Find 12pm on the horizontal axis 2) look at the diagonal line that starts from the 12pm point on the horizontal axis and that goes upwards to the right 3) the lines that lay on that diagonal line are the events that start at 12pm - in this case it's M and L","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":124831,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C","time_elapsed":815002,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0227e"},"answer":"You look at the x coordinate of the graph, start & and time, look for 12pm once you have located 12pm you move diagonally to the right moving upwards and search for the letters on that line when moving diagonally","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":123608,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5","time_elapsed":1270077,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02297"},"answer":"Follow the line to the left of 12 pm and see if there are any dots on it.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":73076,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9","time_elapsed":881021,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022b0"},"answer":"you go to 12 pm and then go diagonally right the whole time ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":34748,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5","time_elapsed":487740,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022c9"},"answer":"YoYou look at where the 12 is on the x axis and trace the line up that is pointed more right","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":72512,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM","time_elapsed":648891,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022e2"},"answer":"start at 12pm on the x axis, take the northeast line and identify all the points along that line","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":40771,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH","time_elapsed":414317,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022fb"},"answer":"go to the 12 pm mark on horizontal axis, follow diagonal up towards right, any points on that line segment would be the shifts starting at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221\n221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":78860,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0","time_elapsed":685233,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0232d"},"answer":"look at 12pm on x axis and follow line going up and to the right. Everything on that line starts at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":49342,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO","time_elapsed":511343,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02346"},"answer":"whichever line veering right starting at the 12pm point is the starting line, so anything plotted along that right leaning line starts at 12pm. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":75846,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP","time_elapsed":967726,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0235f"},"answer":"Find 12 pm on the x axis and then follow the diagonal line upwards and rightwards\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"321","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":41533,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F","time_elapsed":707717,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02378"},"answer":"I lI look at the x-axis (time of day), locate where 12 PM is and follow the diagonal line that slants to the right, locating any points along that line.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":71025,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL","time_elapsed":501678,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02391"},"answer":"Follow the line up and right that, 12pm to see what shifts are there","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":136888,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM","time_elapsed":938899,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023aa"},"answer":"First locate 12pm on the x-axis the follow the diagonal to the right of it. Any event starting at that time will be along that line.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":68105,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3","time_elapsed":582810,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023c3"},"answer":"Go to 12pm on the x-axis and go upward to the right and see what points are on that diagonal line","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":75844,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR","time_elapsed":987587,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023dc"},"answer":"The diagonal line from 12pm to the 8 hour duration line","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":44328,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E","time_elapsed":618851,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023f5"},"answer":"follow the diagonal line","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":15579,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ","time_elapsed":442355,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0240e"},"answer":"Using the right most diagonal line that starts at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":34614,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0","time_elapsed":425648,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02427"},"answer":"To determine what events start at 12 PM you go to the x axis that says 12 PM and you look at the right and left branches it has. This tells us that M and L both start at 12 PM even though they have different shift durations ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":60457,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL","time_elapsed":656693,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02441"},"answer":"I pick the letter closest to 12 PM on the graph","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":34947,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF","time_elapsed":647232,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0245b"},"answer":"gp to 12pm on the bottom of the graph and then trace up until you land on a dot","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":40051,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX","time_elapsed":862312,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02474"},"answer":"Locate 12 PM on the X-axis, then follow the diagonal line going upward-left. All points along that line start at 12 PM.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":98391,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY","time_elapsed":740649,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0248d"},"answer":"At 12 pm B and F start shifts and J ends their shift.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":53073,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796","time_elapsed":692483,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024a7"},"answer":"look at the dot and subtract the hours on the left by the time on the bottom","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":23859,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT","time_elapsed":947995,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024c1"},"answer":"The shifts that line up above 12pm on the x axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":45527,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ","time_elapsed":466658,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024db"},"answer":"LooLook at the X axis to where 12 pm is and then go up the y axis to determine which dots are marked. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":49604,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF","time_elapsed":838353,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024f5"},"answer":"Look at the X-axis for the dots corresponding with the time at 12","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":30404,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P","time_elapsed":614198,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0250f"},"answer":"You can determine what event(s) start at 12pm by first looking at the times at the bottom of the chart. From there you can go upward from 12 and see what dots align.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":40000,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU","time_elapsed":584711,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02529"},"answer":"Which events start at the line angles up to the right at the number 12 on the x-axis start at 12 pm. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":43344,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR","time_elapsed":557465,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02543"},"answer":"Find 12 PM on the x-axis. Trace a vertical line upwards from the 12 PM on the x-axis. All the points on that line begin at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":106930,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW","time_elapsed":742363,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0255d"},"answer":"Drawing a line straight up from the x axis and the given time","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":36067,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74","time_elapsed":754030,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02577"},"answer":"draw a vertical line up from 12PM","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":33561,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8","time_elapsed":509051,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02591"},"answer":"I find 12pm on the horizontal axis and then follow the line that extends from 12pm to the upper right corner of the graph. In this case, M and L start at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":64935,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44","time_elapsed":983485,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025ab"},"answer":"Find 12PM on the bottom axis and follow the diagonal line up and to the right, anything on that line starts at 12PM.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"221","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":42677,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q","time_elapsed":618089,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025c4"},"answer":"SShifts B and G start at 12 pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":31335,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE","time_elapsed":780054,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025de"},"answer":"look at the 12 pm dash and look up","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":18911,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9","time_elapsed":382976,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02612"},"answer":"To find what event(s) start at 12pm, find it on the x-axis, where time of day is located and follow the line in the diagram all the way up. You will find that M and L start at 12 but end at different times. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":105809,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5","time_elapsed":1168112,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02646"},"answer":"follow the 12 pm line that goes up towards the right. any points on that line starts at 12","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":27504,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90","time_elapsed":174531,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02660"},"answer":"find 12 on the bottom and then climb diagonally to the right, so the shifts starting at 12 would be M and L ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":42737,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC","time_elapsed":507342,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02694"},"answer":"vertical dots\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":10982,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6","time_elapsed":356059,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026ae"},"answer":"yyou have to look at the x axis of this graph and find where 12pm is. then you follow that point up the diagonal line until you hit a letter or letters. thoes letters or letter are the shifts or shift that starts at 12 pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":81648,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY","time_elapsed":717521,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026c8"},"answer":"I Look at the line and go up to see which aligns with the 12 pm mark","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":31502,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV","time_elapsed":258626,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026e2"},"answer":"Look at the x axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":8563,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R","time_elapsed":365564,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0274a"},"answer":"draw a vertical line from the 12 pm point and look at which events have start points that intersect with the line. In this case, B and F.\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":84236,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ","time_elapsed":862798,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02764"},"answer":"use the graph, find 12 on the x axis and go up","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":33291,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8","time_elapsed":1271358,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027b2"},"answer":"If the data point is line up with 12 pm on the x axis, that is when it starts","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":59515,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM","time_elapsed":613843,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027cc"},"answer":"loolook at 12 pm on the x axis then move in a straight line upwards until coming to a dot","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":31606,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU","time_elapsed":646950,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027e6"},"answer":"Look Look at the graph where it says 12p and then look at the line to the right to see which shifts start are 12pm. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":52697,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP","time_elapsed":847727,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02800"},"answer":"I look at the x axis, go to the 12pm time, and move up the graph. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":25899,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500","time_elapsed":484062,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0281a"},"answer":"Shifts that start at 12pm are along the line that goes to the right starting from 12pm, meaning that M and L start at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":119852,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1","time_elapsed":749430,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02834"},"answer":"You look at 12 pm on the x axis and look at the number above it that occur along the same line on the y axis.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":29594,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX","time_elapsed":756589,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0284e"},"answer":"if the left line of the dot begins at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":36163,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE","time_elapsed":614489,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02868"},"answer":"You look at B and F see they are parallel points to 12 pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":31536,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3","time_elapsed":399145,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02882"},"answer":"go to 12pm on the x axis and move up vertically to see which events are on that line","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":32320,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H","time_elapsed":594055,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0289c"},"answer":"go to 12pm on the X axis and go directly up to see which evnts are aligned ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":22760,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT","time_elapsed":269796,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d028b6"},"answer":"I ignore the diagonal lines and look straight above to see which events are along the 12pm vertical line","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":28717,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE","time_elapsed":802754,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0291e"},"answer":"Follow the line going up and to the right (diagonally) from the 12pm point on the x-axis. The points that fall on this line are shifts that start at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":165799,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T","time_elapsed":736443,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02938"},"answer":"Whichever letters align with 12pm right above the horizontal axis (B and F in this case, based on my interpretation of the graph).","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":103063,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH","time_elapsed":2015618,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02952"},"answer":"Looking for the letters on the graph that have lined up with 12pm (F and B)","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":36578,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O","time_elapsed":517784,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0296c"},"answer":"Look at what points match the point of 12 pm based on the X-axis.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":49499,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5","time_elapsed":584089,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02986"},"answer":"Vertical axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":11916,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC","time_elapsed":1253084,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029a0"},"answer":"Look at the bottom where time of day is and find 12pm. Afterwards, look up to see which dots are aligned with 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":73099,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU","time_elapsed":481224,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029ba"},"answer":"F & B start at 12 because the dots are aligned with 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":54264,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0","time_elapsed":1404111,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029d4"},"answer":"The left line moving up and to the right indicate the start time of shifts, so by finding the coordinating point and left line at 12pm, you can find what shifts start at that time","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":87212,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT","time_elapsed":866689,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029ee"},"answer":"Oh no i read the x axis wrong, 12pm is the vertex of the diamond part of the graph not the one before. From there you go up the y axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":55755,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP","time_elapsed":586980,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a3c"},"answer":"Look at the x axis (start and end time (time of day) go to 12pm on that axis scan up and you will located the two shifts that start at 12 pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":87320,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK","time_elapsed":1558678,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a56"},"answer":"look at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":38117,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ","time_elapsed":754846,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a70"},"answer":"Look Look at x axis and see which letter starts there/ has a point","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":26096,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O","time_elapsed":656702,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a8a"},"answer":"12 pm on the x-axis going up are the shifts that start at 12 pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":38616,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8","time_elapsed":814827,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02abe"},"answer":"LookI looked at X-axis and look for 12 pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":24391,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM","time_elapsed":739556,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ad8"},"answer":"Go to the x-axis and find 12 PM, then follow a vertical line up and any shifts along that line start then. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":107473,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT","time_elapsed":644217,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b0c"},"answer":"The line that starts at 12 that is diagonally shooting to the right starting from the 12 point, any dots on that line start at 12. Its hard to describe how I determined it.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":88452,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K","time_elapsed":692210,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b26"},"answer":"","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-9.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":8152,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7","time_elapsed":462176,"trial_index":22,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020c6"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":48093,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020c7"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15283,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020c8"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":19684,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020c9"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9861,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020ca"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":28342,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020cb"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11082,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020cc"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":32911,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020cd"},"answer":"AGK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":52836,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020ce"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":38247,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020cf"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9870,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020d0"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11067,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020d1"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13115,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020d2"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18327,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020d3"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8748,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020d4"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":13899,"session":"a16308330","subject":"WLO69"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020df"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121\n121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":30562,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020e0"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":42611,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020e1"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":23208,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020e2"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121\n121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":13857,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020e3"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121\n121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":36218,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020e4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11258,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020e5"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25782,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020e6"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":57085,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020e7"},"answer":"IEM","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121\n121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":69163,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020e8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9011,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020e9"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":22961,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020ea"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8279,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020eb"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21448,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020ec"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11658,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020ed"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121\n121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":25950,"session":"a1677674","subject":"63VL0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020f8"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":42324,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020f9"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":25644,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020fa"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":17536,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020fb"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":17241,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020fc"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":58627,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020fd"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":33820,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020fe"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":7,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":37382,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d020ff"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":47164,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02100"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":37580,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02101"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":13550,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02102"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11597,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02103"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7589,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02104"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":11700,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02105"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11311,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02106"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":20280,"session":"a16348482","subject":"LZSME"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02111"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":15027,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02112"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10937,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02113"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16942,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02114"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":43898,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02115"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":29984,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02116"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":19683,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02117"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24543,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02118"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":57486,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02119"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":20468,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d0211a"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10414,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d0211b"},"answer":"JM","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10865,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d0211c"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":17042,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d0211d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18577,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d0211e"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7918,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d0211f"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":15224,"session":"a16128348","subject":"YRELO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d0212a"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":45395,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d0212b"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10894,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d0212c"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":7447,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d0212d"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":6532,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d0212e"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":11844,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d0212f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15177,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02130"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":27216,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02131"},"answer":"AG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":24101,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02132"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":62257,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02133"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7380,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02134"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8194,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02135"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7834,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02136"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":9918,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02137"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7933,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944a732570cf33d02138"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":9886,"session":"a15769204","subject":"47SB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0218e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":33085,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0218f"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12635,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02190"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":9167,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02191"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10596,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02192"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":12323,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02193"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13256,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02194"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":22109,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02195"},"answer":"AK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":35597,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02196"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16753,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02197"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10071,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02198"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":5776,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02199"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7928,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0219a"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":14592,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0219b"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8240,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0219c"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16865,"session":"a15458549","subject":"DGVGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021a7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":41108,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021a8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":32246,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021a9"},"answer":"AF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":74534,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021aa"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":34173,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021ab"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":138748,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021ac"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12790,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021ad"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":75210,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021ae"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":186766,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021af"},"answer":"IM","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":141702,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021b0"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":39719,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021b1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":1487203,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021b2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":18025,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021b3"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17792,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021b4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":42708,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021b5"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":36166,"session":"a13190800","subject":"TE7JZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021c0"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":69882,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021c1"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8697,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021c2"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":8400,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021c3"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9567,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021c4"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":18956,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021c5"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":51227,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021c6"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28970,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021c7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":35611,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021c8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16914,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021c9"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11360,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021ca"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6219,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021cb"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9609,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021cc"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21429,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021cd"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7837,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021ce"},"answer":"CK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":19466,"session":"a15435687","subject":"1H0SY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021d9"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":21108,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021da"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17995,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021db"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13880,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021dc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":42128,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021dd"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":27688,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021de"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15115,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021df"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":36526,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021e0"},"answer":"IJEFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":36265,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021e1"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26591,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021e2"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10973,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021e3"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11078,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021e4"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":51304,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021e5"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23990,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021e6"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":5633,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021e7"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":12984,"session":"a15839275","subject":"9PELV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021f2"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":10702,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021f3"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9557,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021f4"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11701,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021f5"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":7379,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021f6"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":12658,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021f7"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15912,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021f8"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":12797,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021f9"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":36997,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021fa"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22156,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021fb"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10915,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021fc"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":22706,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021fd"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10726,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021fe"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":12986,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d021ff"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10510,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02200"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":13371,"session":"a16031916","subject":"UDSVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0220b"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":43203,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0220c"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14348,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0220d"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":10288,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0220e"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10284,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0220f"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":18005,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02210"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9001,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02211"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":33719,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02212"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":91701,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02213"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":38132,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02214"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":13149,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02215"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9225,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02216"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10726,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02217"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":19261,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02218"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":12928,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02219"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":20610,"session":"hollanlab","subject":"5N035"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02224"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":180359,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02225"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":51100,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02226"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":22193,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02227"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16240,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02228"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":91223,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02229"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8967,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0222a"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":34994,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0222b"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":84549,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0222c"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":39423,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0222d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":20664,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0222e"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10349,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0222f"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":19898,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02230"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":12174,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02231"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":15715,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02232"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":111081,"session":"a15673149","subject":"1SY41"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0223d"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":40139,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0223e"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":6807,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0223f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":7734,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02240"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":5383,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02241"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":30994,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02242"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":3978,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02243"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"221\n221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18646,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02244"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":98059,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02245"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":35178,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02246"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":26114,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02247"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7151,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02248"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":4892,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02249"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":12765,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0224a"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7350,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0224b"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16568,"session":"16132934","subject":"Q20EE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02256"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":139697,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02257"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17835,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02258"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":7115,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02259"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":12609,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0225a"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":40317,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0225b"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15631,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0225c"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":53859,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0225d"},"answer":"AG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":84632,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0225e"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":55692,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0225f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":19172,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02260"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":22780,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02261"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":16798,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02262"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28572,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02263"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":13832,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02264"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":24012,"session":"a15378348","subject":"ZV99C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0226f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":73253,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02270"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":19423,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02271"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26536,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02272"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":26294,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02273"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":118328,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02274"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":45060,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02275"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":78710,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02276"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":104796,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02277"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":88267,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02278"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":48038,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02279"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":56731,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0227a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":30188,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0227b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":50521,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0227c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":24960,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0227d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":38008,"session":"a15960387","subject":"SQ3V5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02288"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":38688,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02289"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16352,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0228a"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13493,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0228b"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10228,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0228c"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":47558,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0228d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8469,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0228e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":32075,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0228f"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":173353,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02290"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22490,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02291"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":20386,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02292"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6756,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02293"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12664,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02294"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29530,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02295"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":27937,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02296"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":6778,"session":"a15928667","subject":"CPRP9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022a1"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":44265,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022a2"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13135,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022a3"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":7893,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022a4"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":13097,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022a5"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":21809,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022a6"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":14887,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022a7"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":29854,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022a8"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":11,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":83411,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022a9"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":40991,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022aa"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11864,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022ab"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9755,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022ac"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8972,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022ad"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":14076,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022ae"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9542,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022af"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":12006,"session":"a15543958","subject":"FW9D5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022ba"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":51755,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022bb"},"answer":"KE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":29251,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022bc"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":42721,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022bd"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":30042,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022be"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":18533,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022bf"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10954,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022c0"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":38108,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022c1"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":85972,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022c2"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":41306,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022c3"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12902,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022c4"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11314,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022c5"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5448,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022c6"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":81419,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022c7"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":14480,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022c8"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":9254,"session":"a15503974","subject":"0C5DM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022d3"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":26150,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022d4"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10399,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022d5"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11149,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022d6"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":8094,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022d7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":12378,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022d8"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7564,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022d9"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":34600,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022da"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":44439,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022db"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":50897,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022dc"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7269,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022dd"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8857,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022de"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8433,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022df"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18422,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022e0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":5200,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022e1"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":14790,"session":"a15664520","subject":"07MCH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022ec"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":37840,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022ed"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":32139,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022ee"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":21720,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022ef"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":18134,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022f0"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":21107,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022f1"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8352,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022f2"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15120,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022f3"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":73291,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022f4"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":40237,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022f5"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":17359,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022f6"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14556,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022f7"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9067,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022f8"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":16862,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022f9"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11413,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d022fa"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221\n221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":36477,"session":"a15644634","subject":"SGEJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0231e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24450,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0231f"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14056,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02320"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14433,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02321"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":13821,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02322"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":14406,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02323"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13442,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02324"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28034,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02325"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":49893,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02326"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":58684,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02327"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":18925,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02328"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8568,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02329"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8028,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0232a"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":13368,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0232b"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10418,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0232c"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":13428,"session":"a16143137","subject":"LNVKO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02337"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":67865,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02338"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8630,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02339"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":10450,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0233a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":11843,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0233b"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":10838,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0233c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":35223,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0233d"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17652,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0233e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":41273,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0233f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":47160,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02340"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7063,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02341"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13059,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02342"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5785,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02343"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23235,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02344"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6377,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02345"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16070,"session":"a15564584","subject":"GXWDP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02350"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":21554,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02351"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9139,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02352"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":15765,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02353"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10268,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02354"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":58097,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02355"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":24052,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02356"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25310,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02357"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":43478,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02358"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":39954,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02359"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":68933,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0235a"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10252,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0235b"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10600,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0235c"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":47820,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0235d"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"321","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":75760,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0235e"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"321","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":47913,"session":"a16294943","subject":"E0G9F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d02369"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":23792,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0236a"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":34480,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0236b"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16676,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0236c"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":18497,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0236d"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":15653,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0236e"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10119,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944b732570cf33d0236f"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":6,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":79382,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02370"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":25705,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02371"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":40305,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02372"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8121,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02373"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15825,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02374"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8585,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02375"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":10957,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02376"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8250,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02377"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":15814,"session":"a16622527","subject":"JPZWL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02382"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":58410,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02383"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":54507,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02384"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26406,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02385"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":15874,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02386"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":97776,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02387"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12585,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02388"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":111357,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02389"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":60907,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0238a"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":65862,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0238b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":16116,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0238c"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15808,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0238d"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":19852,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0238e"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":27166,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0238f"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11317,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02390"},"answer":"AGC","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":50847,"session":"a15505662","subject":"LCFZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0239b"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":60001,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0239c"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":22565,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0239d"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":8365,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0239e"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":19798,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0239f"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":47071,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023a0"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9476,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023a1"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":71028,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023a2"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":47977,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023a3"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":29750,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023a4"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9101,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023a5"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10484,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023a6"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8077,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023a7"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":19364,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023a8"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8518,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023a9"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":22756,"session":"a15815721","subject":"7K6V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023b4"},"answer":"FKUDEGB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":7,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":112767,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023b5"},"answer":"KE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":46783,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023b6"},"answer":"FDE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":49181,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023b7"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":14,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":107202,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023b8"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":30680,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023b9"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15936,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023ba"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":54101,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023bb"},"answer":"IJCOHZND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":8.5,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":94467,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023bc"},"answer":"IJE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":74915,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023bd"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":53084,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023be"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":17324,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023bf"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13849,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023c0"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":15811,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023c1"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":12936,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023c2"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":27548,"session":"a15583685","subject":"KFXNR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023cd"},"answer":"IO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":65726,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023ce"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11624,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023cf"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":33032,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023d0"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10047,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023d1"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":32055,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023d2"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10962,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023d3"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":31181,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023d4"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":98689,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023d5"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":59263,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023d6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12061,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023d7"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":18617,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023d8"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":15557,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023d9"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23719,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023da"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6763,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023db"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":10572,"session":"a15578823","subject":"U794E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023e6"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":45183,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023e7"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13757,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023e8"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14241,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023e9"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10073,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023ea"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":11028,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023eb"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13268,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023ec"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30364,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023ed"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":28477,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023ee"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":60210,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023ef"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":18140,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023f0"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":16962,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023f1"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9562,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023f2"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24099,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023f3"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8240,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023f4"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":43134,"session":"a16176734","subject":"RRQXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d023ff"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":9246,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02400"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12668,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02401"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11769,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02402"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":11328,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02403"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":6754,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02404"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9575,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02405"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25534,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02406"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":56274,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02407"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":107881,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02408"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7380,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02409"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":16261,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0240a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6905,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0240b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18387,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0240c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7417,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0240d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":12902,"session":"a15588293","subject":"B0QF0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02418"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":27662,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02419"},"answer":"KE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":40245,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0241a"},"answer":"AFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":57815,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0241b"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":35767,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0241c"},"answer":"AFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":32402,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0241d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13151,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0241e"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":45093,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0241f"},"answer":"IO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":39599,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02420"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":31492,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02421"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":23303,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02422"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":37347,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02423"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":14251,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02424"},"answer":"CH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":25414,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02425"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":27078,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02426"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":28629,"session":"a15428617","subject":"OUCFL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02432"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":37974,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02433"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":28856,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02434"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16436,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02435"},"answer":"AFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":23391,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02436"},"answer":"AFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":17033,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02437"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9430,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02438"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":39976,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02439"},"answer":"IEF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":7,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":118577,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0243a"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":8919,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0243b"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8399,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0243c"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9482,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0243d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12055,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0243e"},"answer":"JXND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":46037,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0243f"},"answer":"IBO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10176,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02440"},"answer":"JXND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":17130,"session":"a16577976","subject":"KT7ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0244c"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":45381,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0244d"},"answer":"AK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":52483,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0244e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":42842,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0244f"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":32518,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02450"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":64694,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02451"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10286,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02452"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":94243,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02453"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":73413,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02454"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":49997,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02455"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":21737,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02456"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":26666,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02457"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9799,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02458"},"answer":"CO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28089,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02459"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7580,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0245a"},"answer":"CX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":98600,"session":"a15504468","subject":"US1HX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02465"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":47608,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02466"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":23469,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02467"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":27612,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02468"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":20635,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02469"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":42613,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0246a"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":97987,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0246b"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":46635,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0246c"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":45749,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0246d"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18267,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0246e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11026,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0246f"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":21945,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02470"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":20284,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02471"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20221,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02472"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11817,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02473"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":18687,"session":"a16623408","subject":"P1STY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0247e"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":28180,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0247f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9895,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02480"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":29892,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02481"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":40338,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02482"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":101069,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02483"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8670,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02484"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":41754,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02485"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":57320,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02486"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":38954,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02487"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":67063,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02488"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8680,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02489"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7669,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0248a"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21493,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0248b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":30745,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0248c"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":36087,"session":"a16333285","subject":"ZL796"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02498"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":137973,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02499"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":233249,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0249a"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":86540,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0249b"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9655,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0249c"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":30207,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0249d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7806,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0249e"},"answer":"MO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":57951,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0249f"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":89897,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024a0"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":15432,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024a1"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":5936,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024a2"},"answer":"XZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":34557,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024a3"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":49866,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024a4"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17742,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024a5"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9817,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024a6"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":36733,"session":"a15515318\na15515318","subject":"ACEXT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024b2"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":54902,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024b3"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":7382,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024b4"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":10685,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024b5"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":28538,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024b6"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":32095,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024b7"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7079,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024b8"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":9352,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024b9"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":23264,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024ba"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":10260,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024bb"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":28653,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024bc"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":5347,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024bd"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3292,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024be"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":36346,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024bf"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":63989,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024c0"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":27960,"session":"a16121250","subject":"SGTQJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024cc"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":20634,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024cd"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11497,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024ce"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16072,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024cf"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":46944,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024d0"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":115158,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024d1"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7787,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024d2"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19612,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024d3"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":48892,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024d4"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":13218,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024d5"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":23710,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024d6"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":22441,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024d7"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":18234,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024d8"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":61869,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024d9"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":33672,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024da"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":46472,"session":"a17213518\na17213518","subject":"WWMDF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024e6"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24853,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024e7"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17862,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024e8"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14792,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024e9"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":32021,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024ea"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":24118,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024eb"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":14143,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024ec"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":88685,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024ed"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":27866,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024ee"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":24757,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024ef"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":59342,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024f0"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10091,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024f1"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":22096,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024f2"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28650,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024f3"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":44412,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d024f4"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":6330,"session":"a16561685","subject":"ALN2P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02500"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":25579,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02501"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11337,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02502"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":29546,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02503"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":38420,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02504"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":58943,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02505"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8038,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02506"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16887,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02507"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":48892,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02508"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":23640,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02509"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":22357,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0250a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11627,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0250b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5295,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0250c"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28347,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0250d"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":45700,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0250e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":37960,"session":"a15428815","subject":"TD0NU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0251a"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":73987,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0251b"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11244,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0251c"},"answer":"AH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18444,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0251d"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":11825,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0251e"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":15118,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0251f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":16383,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02520"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":32776,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02521"},"answer":"AG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":50255,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02522"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":74726,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02523"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9145,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02524"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7681,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02525"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9781,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02526"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":27388,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02527"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8025,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02528"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16396,"session":"a16797648","subject":"431GR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02534"},"answer":"AI","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":59061,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02535"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":69647,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02536"},"answer":"AI","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":28591,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02537"},"answer":"OF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":57980,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02538"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":87621,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02539"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12830,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0253a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":22316,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0253b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":46675,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0253c"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":34844,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0253d"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":28570,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0253e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9576,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0253f"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6231,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02540"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":19626,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02541"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":24923,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02542"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":40702,"session":"a15882706","subject":"5TMTW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0254e"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":11620,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0254f"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":78765,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02550"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":67458,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02551"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":78291,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02552"},"answer":"HK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":27431,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02553"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11027,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02554"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25036,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02555"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":58064,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02556"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18136,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02557"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":27608,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02558"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":17546,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02559"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7517,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0255a"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":56204,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0255b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":38031,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0255c"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":63912,"session":"a16843950","subject":"QOR74"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02568"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":37785,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02569"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15152,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0256a"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12577,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0256b"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":27367,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0256c"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":40226,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0256d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13053,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0256e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18203,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0256f"},"answer":"IJE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":16673,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02570"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26410,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02571"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":57243,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02572"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10215,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02573"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11734,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02574"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17541,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02575"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":38119,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02576"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":41496,"session":"a15481598","subject":"HUNJ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02582"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":86642,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02583"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10227,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02584"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":5280,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02585"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":7410,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02586"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":16058,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02587"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":5324,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02588"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":23340,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02589"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":51421,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0258a"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22527,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0258b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7036,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0258c"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7536,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0258d"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6992,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0258e"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":9706,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0258f"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9524,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02590"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":8924,"session":"a17236014","subject":"Q7A44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0259c"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":36622,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0259d"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":24355,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0259e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":32821,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0259f"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":22453,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025a0"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":36830,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025a1"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10429,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025a2"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":39553,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025a3"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":71347,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025a4"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":70455,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025a5"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":16313,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025a6"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":18323,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025a7"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":18541,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025a8"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20502,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025a9"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10141,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025aa"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"221","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":21431,"session":"a15462161","subject":"XZ05Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025b5"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":27376,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025b6"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16461,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025b7"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":49214,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025b8"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":77142,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025b9"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":136231,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025ba"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8935,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025bb"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25167,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025bc"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":30801,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025bd"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22739,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025be"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":66614,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025bf"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15116,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025c0"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10322,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025c1"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":31979,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025c2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":50059,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025c3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":44826,"session":"a15461540","subject":"P83KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025cf"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":15477,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025d0"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":28135,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025d1"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14322,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025d2"},"answer":"DB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":18631,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025d3"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":25692,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025d4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13858,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025d5"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":1907,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025d6"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":21874,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025d7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16890,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025d8"},"answer":"PLHZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":17331,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025d9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9419,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025da"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8030,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025db"},"answer":"PLH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":16682,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025dc"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10982,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d025dd"},"answer":"AG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":25535,"session":"a15407629","subject":"QVWU9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02603"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":46473,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02604"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":57048,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02605"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18674,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02606"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":42651,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02607"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":93152,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02608"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":34623,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02609"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":80325,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0260a"},"answer":"AGK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":97494,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0260b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":38567,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0260c"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9682,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0260d"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":31331,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0260e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10645,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0260f"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":33383,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02610"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":16157,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02611"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":6.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":316628,"session":"a16328170\na16328170","subject":"YAZM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02637"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":5379,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02638"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9425,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02639"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":7212,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0263a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9537,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0263b"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":5301,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0263c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8945,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0263d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16301,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0263e"},"answer":"N","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":3359,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0263f"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":3543,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02640"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":2867,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02641"},"answer":"N","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":2275,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02642"},"answer":"N","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":1402,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02643"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":2410,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02644"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6295,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02645"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":7250,"session":"16114839","subject":"8DL90"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02651"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":27720,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02652"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12879,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02653"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":27644,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02654"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":45357,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02655"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":37973,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02656"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7261,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02657"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":56166,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02658"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":45385,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02659"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19974,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0265a"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":18647,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0265b"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":18298,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0265c"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":17654,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0265d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":11851,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0265e"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9662,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0265f"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":10679,"session":"a16524240","subject":"57KJC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02685"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":7700,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02686"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13312,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02687"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14145,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02688"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":35834,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02689"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":25095,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0268a"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6018,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0268b"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":12929,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0268c"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":30639,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0268d"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":15645,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0268e"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":26842,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0268f"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10773,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02690"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3514,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02691"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":38443,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02692"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":18488,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02693"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":1301,"session":"15862635","subject":"YK2A6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0269f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":54865,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026a0"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11158,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026a1"},"answer":"AH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18741,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026a2"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":111597,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026a3"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":77392,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026a4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7325,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026a5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":36243,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026a6"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":23837,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026a7"},"answer":"IE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":176776,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026a8"},"answer":"BO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":2169,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026a9"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":2633,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026aa"},"answer":"FM","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":2148,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026ab"},"answer":"BM","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":3190,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026ac"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":2645,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026ad"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":3130,"session":"a15857484","subject":"0YVPY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026b9"},"answer":"AI","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":23759,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026ba"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15379,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026bb"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":20384,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026bc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":12167,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026bd"},"answer":"AZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":44211,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026be"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10057,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026bf"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16178,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026c0"},"answer":"OLH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":8958,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026c1"},"answer":"COH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":3399,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026c2"},"answer":"GC","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":2549,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026c3"},"answer":"CX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":2777,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026c4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":2978,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026c5"},"answer":"CO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":2597,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026c6"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6054,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026c7"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":3451,"session":"a15977973","subject":"ECJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026d3"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":18227,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026d4"},"answer":"ZHJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15084,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026d5"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":24117,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026d6"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":26657,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026d7"},"answer":"FU","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":23867,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026d8"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":5267,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026d9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":29551,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026da"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":32565,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026db"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16108,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026dc"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":27457,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026dd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7736,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026de"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5181,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026df"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":14436,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026e0"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6917,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d026e1"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":1477,"session":"a16583212","subject":"LS93R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0273b"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":69552,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0273c"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":73147,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0273d"},"answer":"ZHJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":6.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":72152,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0273e"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16936,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0273f"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":211931,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02740"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7241,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02741"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16262,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02742"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":57702,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02743"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":23926,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02744"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":48041,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02745"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8807,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02746"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11373,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02747"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":31459,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02748"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10827,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02749"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":18302,"session":"a15992567","subject":"QNNZZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02755"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":46331,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02756"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":48012,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02757"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":20659,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02758"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":54002,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02759"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":93539,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0275a"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7801,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0275b"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":14899,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0275c"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":42306,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0275d"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19805,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0275e"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":37948,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0275f"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7086,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02760"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3829,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02761"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17960,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02762"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":24274,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02763"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":25421,"session":"a16811213","subject":"K3AE8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027a3"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":20403,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027a4"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10754,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027a5"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":85023,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027a6"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":8677,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027a7"},"answer":"JD","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":70299,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027a8"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8146,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027a9"},"answer":"IJFBXOZND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":9,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":27285,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027aa"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":42125,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027ab"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":21109,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027ac"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":19353,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027ad"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9518,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027ae"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":4443,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027af"},"answer":"EX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":30278,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027b0"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":28571,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027b1"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":70626,"session":"a15449379","subject":"G17YM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027bd"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":18744,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027be"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12998,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027bf"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26686,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027c0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10473,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027c1"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":84910,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027c2"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6991,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027c3"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":8251,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027c4"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":35624,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027c5"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22622,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027c6"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":45357,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027c7"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12921,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027c8"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5359,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027c9"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":74093,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027ca"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":42875,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027cb"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":78790,"session":"a16254358","subject":"A9JCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027d7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":28269,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027d8"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":42117,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027d9"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":19777,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027da"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":58591,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027db"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":82214,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027dc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10524,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027dd"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":41904,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027de"},"answer":"EFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":63023,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027df"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":34097,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027e0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":70007,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027e1"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13633,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027e2"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7113,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027e3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":41603,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027e4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":73363,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027e5"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":75311,"session":"a16219353","subject":"96GEP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027f1"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":25127,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027f2"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15600,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027f3"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":20384,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027f4"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":63879,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027f5"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":105714,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027f6"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10228,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027f7"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":10459,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027f8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":21175,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027f9"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":12909,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027fa"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":31651,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027fb"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6849,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027fc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5222,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027fd"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":13890,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027fe"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":15367,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d027ff"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":27968,"session":"a16622681","subject":"BR500"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0280b"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":13885,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0280c"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":41102,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0280d"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":43222,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0280e"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":65171,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0280f"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":53452,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02810"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6220,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02811"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21576,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02812"},"answer":"AK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":80540,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02813"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":27542,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02814"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":17148,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02815"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10208,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02816"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12472,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02817"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":49024,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02818"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":15635,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02819"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16044,"session":"17012262\na17012262","subject":"OFOB1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02825"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24047,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02826"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":31609,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02827"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":63842,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02828"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":78231,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d02829"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":43290,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0282a"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7859,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0282b"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16757,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0282c"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":46309,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0282d"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":39250,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0282e"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":28209,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944c732570cf33d0282f"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9948,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02830"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6042,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02831"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":80626,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02832"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":83580,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02833"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":84142,"session":"a16783696","subject":"98VDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0283f"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":44230,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02840"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":26188,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02841"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14133,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02842"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":46620,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02843"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":9652,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02844"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":32395,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02845"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":75289,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02846"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":57933,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02847"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":37803,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02848"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12085,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02849"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10809,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0284a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6472,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0284b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":13959,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0284c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8944,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0284d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":20310,"session":"a17235796","subject":"B44PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02859"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":7941,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0285a"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":7539,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0285b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12493,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0285c"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":12823,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0285d"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":44035,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0285e"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12209,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0285f"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20181,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02860"},"answer":"IE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":34568,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02861"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22398,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02862"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11120,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02863"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9013,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02864"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":20266,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02865"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28167,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02866"},"answer":"OHD","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":21299,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02867"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":24137,"session":"a15415850","subject":"VP6G3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02873"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":30612,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02874"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11114,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02875"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16687,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02876"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":86353,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02877"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":72069,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02878"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6547,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02879"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19925,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0287a"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":37045,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0287b"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26325,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0287c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":47504,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0287d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9697,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0287e"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7724,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0287f"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20190,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02880"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":21661,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02881"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":17815,"session":"a14821119\na14821119","subject":"QLO9H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0288d"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":4799,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0288e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":5661,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0288f"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":6618,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02890"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":18483,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02891"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":11077,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02892"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7710,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02893"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":7814,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02894"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":14514,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02895"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":7922,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02896"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11682,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02897"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":5895,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02898"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3077,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02899"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":10823,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0289a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":37797,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0289b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":33249,"session":"a14821119","subject":"5TXOT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d028a7"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":78251,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d028a8"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":23520,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d028a9"},"answer":"AO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16114,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d028aa"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":30823,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d028ab"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":222162,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d028ac"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11175,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d028ad"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":29961,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d028ae"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":40187,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d028af"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18707,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d028b0"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":46426,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d028b1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11721,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d028b2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":4275,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d028b3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":65114,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d028b4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":35915,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d028b5"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":38651,"session":"a16641170","subject":"E9SDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0290f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24046,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02910"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10678,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02911"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":19132,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02912"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":8549,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02913"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":75294,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02914"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9321,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02915"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15400,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02916"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":65755,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02917"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":53381,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02918"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":97152,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02919"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14493,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0291a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6468,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0291b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17471,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0291c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7092,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0291d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":33572,"session":"a16885269\na16885269","subject":"LAZ3T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02929"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":70677,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0292a"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":35674,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0292b"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":119039,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0292c"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":243196,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0292d"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":179562,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0292e"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":37072,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0292f"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":60394,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02930"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":129041,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02931"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":65903,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02932"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":144582,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02933"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":21837,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02934"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":24296,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02935"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":22176,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02936"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":80346,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02937"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":100164,"session":"a16413173","subject":"K9UQH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02943"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":32442,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02944"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15657,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02945"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14554,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02946"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16901,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02947"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":31368,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02948"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7913,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02949"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18394,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0294a"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":40741,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0294b"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":21397,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0294c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":16696,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0294d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14889,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0294e"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8361,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0294f"},"answer":"LH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24610,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02950"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":18054,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02951"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":28256,"session":"a16325198","subject":"8MT4O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0295d"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":11937,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0295e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9646,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0295f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18900,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02960"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":7414,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02961"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":26226,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02962"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":18344,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02963"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28220,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02964"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":46300,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02965"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":29000,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02966"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":47026,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02967"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12322,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02968"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10113,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02969"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29983,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0296a"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":28358,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0296b"},"answer":"GK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":85111,"session":"a16109769","subject":"EZ7J5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02977"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":22353,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02978"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10371,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02979"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":38693,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0297a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":91270,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0297b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":141905,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0297c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7245,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0297d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":31816,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0297e"},"answer":"GCXOLHZND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":9.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":361601,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0297f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":34494,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02980"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":95039,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02981"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6716,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02982"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7097,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02983"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23097,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02984"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":21509,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02985"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":206243,"session":"a16847802","subject":"WB4HC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02991"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":19882,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02992"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":18227,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02993"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":8151,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02994"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10608,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02995"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":9825,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02996"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7699,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02997"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17387,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02998"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":59829,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02999"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":48503,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0299a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7091,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0299b"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7395,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0299c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3883,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0299d"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":50399,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0299e"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":25988,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d0299f"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16019,"session":"a09436222","subject":"WYZCU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029ab"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":44119,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029ac"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11599,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029ad"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26566,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029ae"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":22107,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029af"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":87521,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029b0"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":36953,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029b1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":32503,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029b2"},"answer":"IJE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":157764,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029b3"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22657,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029b4"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":23108,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029b5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12828,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029b6"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":137692,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029b7"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":126023,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029b8"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":57293,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029b9"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":262081,"session":"a16528837","subject":"9S5Z0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029c5"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":43030,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029c6"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":44209,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029c7"},"answer":"JB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":78697,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029c8"},"answer":"DB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":33838,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029c9"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":44430,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029ca"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10370,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029cb"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18260,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029cc"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":51520,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029cd"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":41878,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029ce"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":103757,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029cf"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14358,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029d0"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7093,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029d1"},"answer":"HN","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18760,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029d2"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7704,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029d3"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":26006,"session":"a15889123","subject":"OE3DT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029df"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":22277,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029e0"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13625,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029e1"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":24243,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029e2"},"answer":"OF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":37705,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029e3"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":36449,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029e4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7103,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029e5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16808,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029e6"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":12.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":97109,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029e7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19896,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029e8"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":44380,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029e9"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6056,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029ea"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3505,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029eb"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29502,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029ec"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":22845,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d029ed"},"answer":"BM","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":57936,"session":"a15777676","subject":"1QMGP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a2d"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24356,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a2e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":24101,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a2f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":90506,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a30"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":13680,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a31"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":104877,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a32"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6779,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a33"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17270,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a34"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":124985,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a35"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":42833,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a36"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":93286,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a37"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13342,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a38"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":39584,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a39"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":160643,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a3a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":97040,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a3b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":166658,"session":"a16074760","subject":"E6KMK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a47"},"answer":"CO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":48753,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a48"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13539,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a49"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16712,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a4a"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":24952,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a4b"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":22387,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a4c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":19334,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a4d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":14261,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a4e"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":99553,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a4f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":158226,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a50"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":23624,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a51"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7461,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a52"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3826,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a53"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":92224,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a54"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":23012,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a55"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":68353,"session":"a17184034","subject":"ARCSZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a61"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":15264,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a62"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9017,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a63"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":32381,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a64"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":31710,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a65"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":17463,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a66"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9242,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a67"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17561,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a68"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":23713,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a69"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":15893,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a6a"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":22060,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a6b"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8393,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a6c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5150,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a6d"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":139716,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a6e"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":47017,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a6f"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":135272,"session":"a16608791","subject":"Z461O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a7b"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":48286,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a7c"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":34691,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a7d"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":35108,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a7e"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":79066,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a7f"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":118934,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a80"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10158,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a81"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15187,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a82"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":35085,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a83"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19737,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a84"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":50914,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a85"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12758,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a86"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5662,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a87"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":32851,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a88"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":70465,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02a89"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":64121,"session":"a15404283","subject":"0F1A8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02aaf"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":123912,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ab0"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":72707,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ab1"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":92798,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ab2"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":8905,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ab3"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":58110,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ab4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9859,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ab5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15550,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ab6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":29694,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ab7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":20289,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ab8"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":19846,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ab9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10834,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02aba"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7420,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02abb"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24841,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02abc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":18239,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02abd"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":61328,"session":"a16348868","subject":"F86ZM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ac9"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":16793,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02aca"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":22600,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02acb"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16347,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02acc"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":43128,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02acd"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":77237,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ace"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9608,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02acf"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20101,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ad0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":48157,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ad1"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":36242,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ad2"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":44767,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ad3"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12600,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ad4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10888,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ad5"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23658,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ad6"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":24132,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02ad7"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":28597,"session":"a17174133","subject":"UN6MT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02afd"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":30704,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02afe"},"answer":"KE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":28757,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02aff"},"answer":"AZFHJKUDEGB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":18.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":104923,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b00"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":17479,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b01"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":13249,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b02"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10135,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b03"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19137,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b04"},"answer":"EFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":85508,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b05"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":53451,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b06"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":21267,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b07"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13023,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b08"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":25153,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b09"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17012,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b0a"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":19700,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b0b"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":22284,"session":"a17155299","subject":"CHP0K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b17"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":31853,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b18"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8316,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b19"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14500,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b1a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":34917,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b1b"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":50592,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b1c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13027,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b1d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":31018,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b1e"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":55702,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b1f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":17598,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b20"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11960,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b21"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12489,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b22"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7973,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b23"},"answer":"JX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":33610,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b24"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":19766,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61a1944d732570cf33d02b25"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":2455,"session":"a17243733","subject":"XOZJ7"}]
